<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Carolina Cloud Blog</title>
    <link>https://carolinacloud.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Carolina Cloud Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 05:54:30 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://carolinacloud.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Call Center Transcription: Over 90% Cost Reduction with Better Features</title>
      <link>https://carolinacloud.io/blog/transcription/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 05:54:30 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://carolinacloud.io/blog/transcription/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After six months with Azure OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s Whisper API, a major call center needed a better solution. They were processing hundreds of thousands of minutes of audio per day, and costs were climbing. More importantly, they needed speaker diarization—something the OpenAI API simply didn&amp;rsquo;t offer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Without diarization, they couldn&amp;rsquo;t answer critical performance management questions: What percentage of agents proactively offered a specific solution? What percentage mentioned key product features? Which agents needed coaching on particular topics? These insights were locked behind the technical limitation of not knowing &lt;em&gt;who&lt;/em&gt; said &lt;em&gt;what&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the Carolina Cloud Blog</title>
      <link>https://carolinacloud.io/blog/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://carolinacloud.io/blog/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the official Carolina Cloud blog! We&amp;rsquo;re excited to share our journey building a family-owned cloud platform that puts transparency, performance, and affordability first.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-we-built-carolina-cloud&#34;&gt;Why We Built Carolina Cloud&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As researchers, we experienced firsthand the frustrations of traditional cloud providers: confusing pricing, long cluster queues, and bills that spiraled out of control. We knew there had to be a better way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Carolina Cloud was born from a simple idea: &lt;strong&gt;what if cloud computing was transparent, affordable, and actually designed for the people who use it?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
