<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Carolina Cloud Blog</title>
    <link>https://carolinacloud.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Carolina Cloud Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 05:54:30 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://carolinacloud.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Genomics Pipeline: Saving 70% Per Month with a Superior Development Experience</title>
      <link>https://carolinacloud.io/blog/genomics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 05:54:30 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://carolinacloud.io/blog/genomics/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A genomics startup with less than a year of runway needed to build a pipeline for processing cattle genomic data—merging chromosomal data from hundreds of animals to identify genetic markers. They&amp;rsquo;d been using AWS HealthOmics for other genomics tasks, but as they evaluated their options for this greenfield project, two problems emerged: the cost would be prohibitive, and the developer experience would make iteration nearly impossible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is the story of how they built their pipeline on Carolina Cloud&amp;rsquo;s bare metal Threadripper infrastructure and gained the development velocity they desperately needed—with 70% cost savings as a bonus.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Call Center Transcription: Over 90% Cost Reduction with Better Features</title>
      <link>https://carolinacloud.io/blog/transcription/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 05:54:30 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://carolinacloud.io/blog/transcription/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After six months with Azure OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s Whisper API, a major call center needed a better solution. They were processing hundreds of thousands of minutes of audio per day, and costs were climbing. More importantly, they needed speaker diarization—something the OpenAI API simply didn&amp;rsquo;t offer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Without diarization, they couldn&amp;rsquo;t answer critical performance management questions: What percentage of agents proactively offered a specific solution? What percentage mentioned key product features? Which agents needed coaching on particular topics? These insights were locked behind the technical limitation of not knowing &lt;em&gt;who&lt;/em&gt; said &lt;em&gt;what&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
